It's now the end of all the visions that we had
私たちが抱いていたビジョンはもう終わり。
You were a friend, but we were never meant to be
あなたは友達だったけれど、私たちは決してそうなる運命ではなかった。
Because the lane we took is now a broken path
私たちが通った道は、今は壊れた道だから。
I walk away now, to resign you as a memory
あなたを思い出として諦めるために、私は今立ち去る。
Did it hurt? To think I'd failed to care
痛かった？ 私が気にかけなかったことを考えると、
I know you felt that wasn't fair
あなたはそれが不公平だと感じていたことがわかります。
And you were weeping, gripping my tainted heart
そしてあなたは泣いて、私の汚れた心をつかんでいました。
While I simply sigh from afar, asking...
その間、私は遠くからただため息をつき、尋ねています...
Why is it comforting to know that we are done?
私たちの終わりを知ることはなぜ慰めになるのでしょうか？
Although these feelings are bitter and blunt
苦くて露骨な感情だけど
It feels immoral that I celebrate alone
ひとりで祝うのは不道徳な気がする
The relief is real
安堵は本当
I'm freed from your embrace, oh darlin'
君の抱擁から解放された、オー・ダーリン
Na na na~♪
ナナナ～♪ いつ
I'm still afraid to show when I would be upset
怒るかを表に出すのがまだ怖い
'Cause my emotions were for entertaining you
僕の感情は君を楽しませるためのものだったから
I saw the crossroads that leads back to where we met
出会った場所に戻る岐路を見た 罪悪
Though I feel guilty, don't return me to that avenue
感は感じるけど、あの道に戻さないで
Did it hurt? To think I'd failed to care
痛かったかな？ 私が気にかけなかったと思うと、
I know you felt that wasn't fair
あなたはそれが不公平だと感じていたことがわかります。
And you were weeping, gripping my tainted heart
そしてあなたは泣いて、私の汚れた心をつかんでいました。
While I simply sigh from afar, asking...
その間、私は遠くからただため息をつき、尋ねています...
Why is it comforting to know that we are done?
私たちの関係が終わったと知ることはなぜ慰めになるのでしょうか。
Although these feelings are bitter and blunt
これらの感情は苦くて鈍いけれど、
It feels immoral that I celebrate alone
一人で祝うのは不道徳な気がする。
The relief is real
安堵は本当。
I'm freed from your embrace, oh darlin'
あなたの抱擁から解放された、ああダーリン。
I feel disgusted knowing that I hold a smile
笑顔を浮かべていることに気づき、うんざりする。
'Cause all these questions suffocate this heart of mine
なぜなら、これらの疑問のすべてが私の心を窒息させるから。
You said it had to be you,
あなたはそれがあなたでなければならないと言った、
who should plan all my future routes
私の将来の道筋をすべて計画するのはあなたでなければならないとあなたは言った。
Am I wrong to want to walk with someone else?
他の誰かと一緒に歩きたいと思うのは間違っているだろうか？
Wow - whoa - oh
わあ、おお、ああ。これで
Why is it comforting to know that we are done?
終わったと知ると、なぜ安心するのだろう？
Although these feelings are bitter and blunt
この感情は苦くて鈍いけれど、
It feels immoral that I celebrate alone
一人で祝うのは不道徳な気がする。
The relief is real
安堵は本当。
I'm freed from your embrace, oh darlin'
あなたの抱擁から解放されたの、ダーリン
(Ad-lib)
（アドリブ）